ahalife.com 2018-09-24

# Privacy Policy | AHAlife

Effective date: January 24, 2014 

Thank you for visiting Ahalife.com. AHAlife Holdings Inc. ("AHAlife," "we" or "us"), is committed to keeping our customers informed about how we use the information we gather from you through the use of our website, Ahalife.com (the "Site"), and through our products, services and applications offered on or off the Site (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). Our commitment to you as a valued customer is to provide you with an exciting, safe and personalized experience. As part of this commitment to you, we have created this privacy policy to inform you about how we collect, use and share your personal information. In addition, we explain the steps we take to secure your personal information. By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies described in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use and share your information in the following ways. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services. 

Remember that your use of AHAlife’s Services is at all times subject to the 

, which incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Privacy Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the 

. 

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize, provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you and allow other users to contact you, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below. 

Other sites accessible through our Site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that our Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linked to our Sites are not covered by this Policy. 

We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a notice on the Site and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. 

Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide our visitors with an easy, efficient, and customized online experience. 

In order to better provide you with products and services, our Site collects the following types of information: 

_Financial Information:_

We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. 

_Information Collected Automatically:_

Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, device identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Services, and the page or feature you requested. 

Cookies: 

Cookies are pieces of data that we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to identify your browser and/or device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. Websites typically use temporary cookies called "session" cookies to ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page within one site and that any information you have entered is remembered. For example, if an e-commerce site did not use session cookies then items placed in a shopping basket would disappear by the time you reach the checkout. Websites also use "persistent" cookies to enable a website to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services offered, and allowing us to better customize our services for you. AHAlife attempts to install both persistent and session cookies when a user arrives at our Site. We use cookies to track what users view, collect, purchase, like, favorite and other interactions with the Services. Users have the option to accept or disable cookies at any time through their browsers. Visit the "help" portion of your toolbar for more information. If you block or refuse to accept cookies, or delete cookies between visits to the Site, you may not be able to access or use certain features or functions of our Site. Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your browser or device, when you click on ads that appear on the Services. Also, if you click on a link to a third party website or service, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and we aren’t responsible for their privacy policies and practices. 

Clear GIFs: 

At times we employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit or the benefit of a third-party to help us or such third-party measure advertising effectiveness. Clear GIFs help us better manage content on our Site by informing us of what content is effective. These clear GIFs allow us to measure the usage of our Site by our visitors and the effectiveness of certain communications and marketing campaigns. 

Non Personally Identifiable Information: 

"Non Personally Identifiable Information" (don’t worry, it’s not as complicated as it sounds) refers to information that does not identify a specific individual by itself or in combination with other information. We may gather certain demographic information about you such as age, date of birth, gender, as well as consumer purchasing and preference information based upon how you shop on and navigate our Site. This information may be compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the website’s Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. 

When we collect the usage information described above, we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, we may use Non Personally Identifiable Information for testing or debugging purposes, or to analyze request usage patterns, and other customer behavior so that we may enhance our Site, products and services, and for our marketing purposes. We may also use this data to make suggestions for products and services in order to make the Services more relevant and interesting to you. 

Information You Provide Us: 

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, mailing address, zip code, telephone number, mobile phone number, and other contact information, including information associated with recipients of purchases you may make, when you register with us, order a product or service, fill out surveys, correspond with us, or otherwise volunteer information, for instance, through the use of one of our interactive services (such as blogs, commenting, message boards, product submissions, Q&As). With this information, we can fill your service and product orders and better provide you with personalized services. If you contact us by telephone, email or letter, we may keep a record of your contact information, correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with our Site, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. If you provide us feedback through our Site or by email, we may ask for your name and email address in order to send you a reply. If other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or purchases on our Site, or if you are the recipient of products sent by another customer, we may keep the information in a file specific to you. We may also use information to notify consumers about updates to our Site, to complete user initiated transactions, to trace false orders and to contact consumers directly. 

If you provide your third-party account credentials to us or otherwise sign in to the Services through a third party site or service, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy; for example, signing into the Site through Facebook Connect. 

We may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you promotional email offers on behalf of other businesses, or email you about your use of the Services. If you no longer wish to receive such communications, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions that appear in every e-mail, or modify your settings when you’re logged in under the “me” tab on the website. Once we have processed your request, we will not send you promotional emails with respect to products and/or services offered by us through the Site of which you had opted out unless you opt back in to receiving such communications. Please note that even if we stop sending promotional e-mails to you following a request to unsubscribe, we may continue to send you operational emails, which contain information about your order. So keep in mind, if you purchase products on your site, you’ll be receiving operational e-mails when we have important communication to share. 

Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, we do not sell, trade or rent your Personal Information in personally identifiable form collected through our Services to others. However, we may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section: 

_Affiliated Businesses:_ In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell or provide products or services to you through or in connection with the Services (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such businesses’ or websites’ policies. 

_Agents:_ We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, for tracking purposes, to charge your credit card, fill your order, improve the functionality of our Site, customize our marketing efforts, perform statistical and data analyses, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us, or to provide us with other services we request. Unless we tell you differently, these third parties may not use your Personally Identifiable Information other than to provide the services requested by us. 

_Aggregated Personal Information That’s No Longer Personally Identifiable:_ We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information, such as aggregated or segmented statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information, to our partners, who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual. 

_User Profile and Submissions:_ Certain user profile information, including your name, location, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Services, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services or address your request for our services. Your account privacy settings may allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Please remember that any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by anyone. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Services and other users can contact you through messages and comments. 

_Financial Information:_ As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business. 

_Protection of Us and Others:_ We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe in good faith is necessary to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; enforce or apply our Terms of Use (

) and other agreements; or to protect or defend the rights, property, or safety of our users, other and ourselves. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful 

_Business Transfers:_ We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We employ industry-standard electronic, physical and administrative measures and techniques to protect the security of the information you submit to us. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personally Information or otherwise. Credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking institutions, process agents, distribution institutions and our vendors. They receive the information they need to verify and authorize your credit card transactions and to ship your order. When you input your credit card information for online purchases, we offer secured server transactions that encrypt your information in transit to thwart someone from intercepting it and misusing it. When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server and will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us: 

  * name and password
  * email address
  * location
  * user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please 

_contact us_

. 

In certain circumstances under California law, consumer customers of AHAlife who are California residents are entitled to certain information regarding any personally identifiable information (as defined by certain California laws) we may share with direct marketing companies. Personally identifiable information generally is defined under California law as information that identifies specifics about an individual and can be used to identify, contact, or locate an individual including that individual’s name, mailing address, telephone number, mobile phone number, email address and other identification and contact information. If you are an eligible customer of AHAlife and would like to receive a list detailing the types of personally identifiable information we share with direct marketing companies and the names and addresses of all direct marketing companies that we provide personally identifiable information to, please _contact us_. We will respond to any request for information at such email address within thirty (30) days. 

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have inadvertently gathered Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13, we shall erase such information from our records and terminate the applicable account(s) promptly. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please _contact us_. 

You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features. 

You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by 

_contacting us_

. Some information may remain in our records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

If you have any questions regarding our Policy or privacy practices, please 

_contact us_

. 

AHAlife Holdings Inc.   
147 Front Street, 2nd Floor   
Brooklyn, NY 11201
